Uh H okay. I can download my
internet is a bit bad today.
One second.
Have to be really quiet today.
So yeah. Hello everyone.
Um
that's what
Hello Ka
hello.
Hope you guys are doing well. So today
I'll
uh try to be quiet as possible.
because my roommate is sleeping and I
don't want to be
too annoying. But yeah, I'll try my best
to be as quiet as possible. So, it's not
a nuisance to I
um call
out even though I am speaking.
Can someone tell me how the audio is?
Do I need to boost it or
can
um just let me know.
I'll try to add a compressor.
I have a vocal compressor. I just do
this.
Um it's low. Okay. I'm gonna switch my
input to my
uh mixer.
Where is it?
In a second
mix. Okay, there you go. Now I'm audio
slow but can't hear it properly. Hold
on.
Now I should be audible and loud enough,
right?
>> I um in a second minute adjust the
volume.
There you go. Now I should be louder.
Apparently my mic volume was 27%age.
What the hell?
Um,
okay. 100%.
Everything seems to be good. I So, yeah.
Um, since I'm audible, I just want to
continue.
Um,
so today I will be playing this game
called Pu
Champions. In Japan, it's known as Pu
Peu Esports.
Uh
since um I am in Japan, my Steam
version, my Steam region is in Japan.
So, um, apparently
I just got to know yesterday
that this game is out on Nintendo Switch
and PS4 and consoles
uh, and Nintendo and DS as well. DS as
well, this game. Yeah. So for the
Nintendo console versions, it's called
Pew Pew Esports in Japan for East Asia
region. But yeah, uh they will uh it's
more like more universal now. So in a
way, even if I'm in Japan, I can still
play the western version or the
universal version and um yeah, matchmake
with other Japanese people and
worldwide. So yeah, I can actually play
with you guys who also have the thingy.
So yeah. Um
you you're such a good whisperer.
Really? I don't know.
Um
then
um
where was I?
Don't think I'm whispering. I'm still
talking. I have to like um talk less.
No, I'm more quieter.
I'm close to the mic. So,
hey, do you want whisper? Whisper. I can
like do this. What the
I can turn off suppression.
I can turn off it.
What the
I could do that, right?
Okay. I think you can still hear from
the
uh what about now?
This is like the
ros.
Oh my god. But yeah, this is like a
voice, I think.
I
um let me switch to like the game. Okay.
Uh if you hear other people
uh voice a noise from my mic, ignore it.
It's my roommates.
Um hi. And for those who are on YouTube
watching the shrimp,
um I want you to Yeah. yesterday figure
discovered this service.
Um,
let me just find it. I have to add the
command.
Stream snipe.com.
Yeah, the one
um
um Okay, copy the link and YouTube chat.
I just have to paste it right.
I'm taking a bit long to start the
stream.
My name already accessed.
Wait, you can't hear me when I actually
whisper. What? Ah, there you go. Can you
uh Why why why is there no raw voice?
What the Can you hear? Oh.
Bro,
where is
that
m
I'm making you guys wait. Sorry. Sorry.
Some technical issues. I just want to
want people to clip from YouTube even
though they took it away. There's an
external service which can actually let
you clip.
So, one second. Let me just adjust this.
Wait.
Uh, you can do a exclamation clip on
YouTube to make it work.
Okay.
Let's start with the game.
Let me switch. Oh, don't mind that. Um.
Um.
I actually open the game and like set up
stuff so I don't have to like worry
about my settings and all those stuff.
Um,
did it
did it announce that I'm live right now?
It didn't, right?
Let me just do that. Okay.
Can you hear the game?
I believe you can.
Um, can I see the comments?
I can't see the comments. Hi. So, menu.
So this game is basically you can say
anime Tetris in a way I guess some cute
um thingy. These these other Tetris
block blocks you can say 1 2 three five
colors I guess. Uh mostly four. It
depends on the game mode. If the game
mode has five colors you'll see five
colors like that.
Um.
Oh, not that.
Hey. Um.
Uh. So, today we're going to just be
practicing.
We'll do so
and we'll do
Um,
I want to do two. I
do. Okay, let's do this. Endurance.
Wait,
these are all the characters you get in
Puyo Puyo. We got
Amit Ammy T Ringo. She's like literally
an apple.
And so
how do you pronounce his name?
Ryui
Ryina
Alli Ragnas.
This is the character I'm going to go
today.
Uh, witch Draco Santores.
Uh, Rishu, Rishuka,
Carango,
Dark Prince, Batman, and Alex. I was
going to say Alex, but yeah, about the
same. Hi.
Um,
where's my earphone? Um,
can you hear the game? Yeah, you can
hear the game, right?
Hi.
Uh, what is this?
Quick drone on earth off. I would love
to have that
background boost
cuz
ah I forgot
that's literally Tetris now.
I have no idea how to play the game,
but yeah, we can do it.
Uh,
I could do that. Yeah,
I could do this. Yeah.
Uh,
that's Ah, I didn't want to do a chain,
but okay.
Ah, that's a chain. I didn't want to do
that. Why? It's fine. It's fine.
Uh, no, no, no. We can explain the top.
It's fine.
Uh,
so the more you play, there's like the
the white ones are garbage ones
apparently. Um
and um
yeah, I just have to make it matching
and make them join it. That's the thing.
Uh
I might lose this.
Uh chain it. No.
Okay, that works.
>> Oh no. I think I'm going to die.
Oh no.
>> What the? We have a chance.
>> Okay. We have a chance. Yep. We have a
chance. Hi.
We do have a chance. I think I suppose
but
I can't speak. So this is like a
conitive game. Yeah. But
I did not mean to do that. But
I can't do this.
What the
I
I realized
Windows
has a noise suppression, the AI one.
That's why
What the
wait?
Okay.
Superior one.
Yeah.
Yes. First chain. That's nice. That's
nice.
I can do like that. Okay.
I can do that.
And uh for this I can smash
that and go there and the green can go
there.
Uh could see that connect.
to the
How should I do this?
That works as well. Uh, get that. Okay,
get that. Open up that
you.
I know it fell over in there. Okay. Open
up that and clear that.
I could you
could
have space actually.
Uh
no no
that's
not
yeah
almost
I have an idea I can do this can do that
and
that comes there and go
player with that and then we do that
drops there.
I need a yellow.
Uh, so they so do they
and it fills that and it connects.
Oo,
I need to learn how to do count. I am
doing counters, but I don't know how to
do
um
I don't know how to do
uh straight line stuff.
Uh chains, that's the word I was looking
for.
Foreign
Uh there
I'm dying. I'm dying. I'm dying.
Shindas.
Oh, don't kill me like that.
Please don't kill me like that.
Oh no.
me.
>> Uh, so
Uh
she kind of
Oh, no. No, no, no, no, no.
Um
I need
what's Oh, that Oh, wait.
I guess. So,
okay.
Um,
okay. do that.
Oh, my first time playing this game is
so densing.
>> So, I can do three chains easily
sometimes if I concentrate enough.
But but I feel like it's hard to do a
fortune.
You have to remember that I'm playing
with a playing with a CPU.
If I was playing with a real person, I
would be dead long ago.
actual real human issu.
Come.
Am I able to clear the field? Oh, yeah.
I got cleaning it up. That's fine.
Uh
I can play up subh
tonight.
Uh, okay.
Ah, no, no, no mistake.
Okay. Fight, fight, fight.
Oh, this is not fun. Oh, no.
No. I'm dead.
Oh, YouTube chat working.
What the?
Uh,
is it working? Oh, it is working.
YouTube chat is working.
What's going
is working?
Ah, I died.
Play game.
It's Yeah, this game is like for big
brain people unlike me.
I'm just good at FPS and everything.
That's how like I have I'm bad at big
brain games.
Uh
but oh yeah so apparently I have I'm
participating a puy puyo uh tournament
um tournament which is um hosted by
Vakone
as part of as part of their uh Vakone
gaming fest. So it's a puyu vtuber clash
India compet uh tournament.
I don't know who my team is, but I'll be
playing this game and like
um
competing with a lot of professional
people who are good at the game or who
are learning the game. I got good by
playing more and more. So I want to
practice and do my best I guess.
What is fever?
I think fever
I think fever is more of uh fastpace
right
company.
That's it.
And do that.
Is it
Uh, that's fine.
>> Clean it up. We can clean it up.
What do they
eat?
Oh, that's two
two clashes. Yeah.
I'm actually right. Um
that
and let me know who uh owns this game.
So if you want to play together, do let
me know in chat if you wish to play
together.
Oh
boy.
Oh my god.
Uh
Then
itsy itsy
Oh
That's all it
uh
can do that.
No, don't give me that. Yeah.
Uh, I can do that. Yep.
No.
Uh.
fever.
Uh,
that was a bad one.
okay.
it.
Uh,
nice.
No, it's okay. We can recover from that.
We can recover from that. Yep, we can
recover from that.
Uh, so what could that
open it up, right? Can do that.
>> Yeah. So,
I can't do this.
Uh let's go there.
Uh
uh this one.
>> Uh so that
I could have got the green there. Ah,
it's fine. That's fine. Let's do
the bank blue.
It's fine. Oh, no.
I cleared that. I cleaned that. Good.
I actually cleaned it good.
Oh my god. No way. I just messed it up.
No way. I just messed it up. I can
recover from that. Yep. I I Yeah,
you have to think a lot. I I suck at
games like this.
Oh.
Oh, no. No. No. No. No. No.
Oh, no. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
Ah.
Then I'll do this.
So
then this
No. Oh, did I mess that up, brother?
Come here. Come here. Come.
Sorry.
I'm having cold cuz it's cold in Japan.
Uh
yeah.
Oh yeah. Yeah. I I can recover. I can
recover. I can recover.
I can recover.
Um
>> yeah, I want that. Yes.
me.
Uh, that's a bro. I can recover from
that. Uh, make sure I do that. He got a
fever. Oh, no. Oh, no.
He got a fever. Oh, no. No. No. No.
Wait. I can I can I can actually
Oh no.
The K9. The K9. The K9. The K9. This is
bad. This is bad. This is bad.
Uh,
can I? No, I cannot recover. Oh
Y
mina.
Um
yeah, I can I can I can
uh
yeah, I can I can I can believe
there's a green coming.
Bring it down and then I can do that.
Uh
I could have ended over there. That
works. Uh, I just need to clean it up.
Yeah. Yeah, that works. Works. Works.
Works. Works. Good to bring it down.
And uh
can clean it up like this.
And that
fever.
And we can do something like this.
That was the bad. That was a bad move.
All right.
Oh, no.
>> Uh, do that.
I can uh something like that.
Bring it. I'm playing the yellow and
uh
I can do that and this.
So
there
uh um uh
okay and do the red thingy over there.
Ah fever. Okay. Uh, fever. It's a fever.
I messed it up. Messed up the fever.
It's okay. The job.
>> Okay. Yellow.
Ah, it's okay. It's fine.
We can recover from that.
Uh, I can do this.
our hands and like
Yep, that's what I wanted. Then we clear
the full thingy and then we do that. And
there's a blue coming. So we can just
put it here.
We could have cleaned it, but it's fine.
That's simple. A red coming.
This
this works there.
Uh,
okay. Fever. Uh, we can do.
Yeah.
So, okay.
That last minute adjustment though.
Ah, I messed up.
Go to the
and
my neck hurts, man. Oh my god. Let me
let me lay back.
Don't do that.
>> Oh, got to
that works.
That works. And that clears the blue.
And I can do that. And
gate
could win the other side of
a hand.
And then we clean it.
Do that.
>> Got a few
Stupid, stupid,
stupid.
Oh my god. How did I mess that up?
I How did I mess that up?
Yeah, I can do that. in this area.
Uh,
okay, that works.
and we can do that.
>> Clean it up.
>> Clean it up. That gets cleaned. And that
gets cleaned as well.
I can't do that. Oh no,
we're in big trouble.
Uh
fever. Okay, that's good.
It's good that I got a fever. I think I
cannot do this.
over.
>> I messed that up.
I thought I Okay, I can recover.
This game is so stressful
and it's an endless thingy.
It's
going to walk with that.
Uh, you
>> uh I got toy
Uhhuh.
Uh.
Oh, bro. No. I can get you back. Watch
me.
Uh.
Uh, brother, I'm in a bench.
Oh no, I'm in a bench.
Oh my god, that was crazy.
That was nice.
Yeah. Bye. Now,
Alex, what's an actual pro player?
Why is there no one here? Replay
style
creator room or
connection up.
Hello cheer effects. Hello
auto play when count to drop. Yeah, come
back assist.
Same prediction.
What is this?
Wait, why am I going? What the uh what
is set count?
Set money bunny.
Uh,
where's to
I don't know how it is to be defeated by
a pro player.
Ah it shows my location.
Yeah, but now people know that I'm from
I'm living in good.
Yada yada yada yada.
Hello.
Oh
tonight.
Wait, why no one playing? I want to
play.
Why no one playing?
Okay.
Why no one play?
Yeah, you need a teammate
again
matchmaking. Um,
skill rating.
Uh, I have to put a room code.
What the How do I do that? How do I know
my room code and stuff?
Back
collection.
Yeah, fine. I'll cancel it. Oh, someone
is here. Someone is serving in country.
Uh D. I want to go with Grace J.
Okay, time to f see me get defeated.
Oh god, it's magic blocks.
But
I'm going to copy him, I think. I don't
know.
Oh god, he's playing so quickly. Oh no.
Ah, quick drop is not here. Ah, that's
why.
Oh Uh,
that's why that's why. Oh my god, he's
playing so well. Oh my god,
I'm so sorry. Uh,
bro, I can't I can't I can't do this.
This is This is a
He's playing fasted.
I'm taking my sweet time.
>> Oh Oh your but your butt your
butt.
Oh no.
Oh, I'm panicking.
Bro,
bruh.
Bro, what is happening on his screen?
Y.
What the hell just happened? Did he do a
mass chain thingy?
Oh my god, look at him go.
Is this how it feels to get defeated
by someone better than you?
Oh god, he's sending more troops. Enemy
troops.
Oh.
Oh. The way he's playing, it's like that
chain type thingy.
Uh, bro, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Br.
Brother. Brother. Chill. Chill. What the
hell?
What the hell?
I don't get it.
I'm playing so slow. Look at him go.
It started.
It started. I'm I'm dying. I'm I'm dead.
brah.
Brother,
he was like, "This guy is not worth it.
V.
What?
Let's go with this guy.
Tokyo. Someone's from Someone from
Tokyo.
Oh god. Japanese players are so pro at
this game. I I can I can I can feel it,
bro. Look at him play. I'm going to get
on. Yeah.
N is dead.
>> The way he's playing systematically like
a pro, it's it's coming to my brain.
Oh no, I'm dead.
Itsyhe
brosy.
It has begun. It has begun. It has
begun. The massacre has begun. Oh, it's
behind. Oh, God. Help me.
Oh my god. What is going on? What the
hell, brother? What the hell?
>> Oh my lord.
What?
Why?
Let me copy him. Ah
It's
yooy
stop.
I feel like he knows that I'm a easy
target easy player.
Um
a has begun.
Yeah,
bro. What's the point to play? He's
Oh my lord.
How do you know how to play the the way
he plays? just like a pro player. The
way he plays is a pro player. Why?
>> He knows. Hello.
The way he plays is he knows how the
game game works.
It's
perfect.
Oh, bro. Stop massacring me.
Look at that.
Ah, bro.
Oh my. It we we going more. Okay.
Yeah, I know. I lost three times.
Oh, bro. He started to massacre me.
Mate, mate, mate, mate, mate. I'll
massacre him. I can do this. I can do
this. I can do this. I can do this. I
learned the I learned the tactics. I
learned the tactics. I learned the
tactics. I learned the tactics.
Um, yeah, I learned the tactics. Oh my
god, I'm getting better.
Oh No.
No.
I did.
How?
Wait. Let me copy him. Let me copy what
he's doing.
Uh, he put it like this, right? Okay.
Then he put it like this again. Then he
put this thing like this. Okay, let me
copy him. He will not. No.
Uh, okay. Where did he put this? Uh,
no. That was wrong. No.
Ah, yada. I did it wrong. No.
Aha, bro. I couldn't copy him in time.
>> The massacre has started again.
Uh, yada.
Uh,
>> bro, I've lost
Okay. I I actually did a
combo. I I did a combo. I did a combo.
Oh my god. I did a combo.
Am
I am I so
>> I feel like if I'm being forced to play
with the with this pro player, I will
improve cuz I'll be like in my Oh, I
actually defeated him. Bro,
I actually defeated him. Okay.
Oh my god. Actually defeated him. Oh my
god. Thank you.
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bro, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
She's done.
>> What?
I got cooked. I got cocky. That's why
I got cocky.
Wait,
what am I doing?
Oh
I got cooked.
Ah,
how do you use your brain to think ahead
in time?
Uh
I uh
oh the breath
Let's
go back. Ow.
Ah.
Yeah.
Hen players.
Okay. Okay.
This guy is from Tokyo, right?
Ah,
>> I didn't want to.
Okay, I do that. Maybe this.
Oh, no, no, no. I can put it there. And
then maybe I can put it like this. Uh, I
can put it there. Okay. Maybe that goes
there. And uh, no, I didn't want to
Uh, I can go there. And uh,
that works. Okay. Uh, yeah. He's uh,
he's he's attacking. He's attacking.
He's attacking.
Uh yada yada yada yada.
I can block him maybe. Uh maybe maybe
bro.
Nah.
How do I How do I do emotes?
Is it Is it going to go forever?
Oh my god. It's gonna go. I mean, it's a
good practice dish.
Getting cooked every single time like
this.
It feels not It doesn't feel bad.
Got the shield.
Yeah. I didn't want to
Oh my god, he's attacking me strong.
I'm kind of understanding that you're
not supposed to chain it in the early
stage. You're supposed to do it in the
medium middle stage.
Oh my god, I died.
>> At least I got one win. Okay.
Yep.
I'll move only when he had Oh
Uh
Jokix, you're too late.
Yes, I defeated him. Let's go.
Oh my god, too. Okay.
Uh, so you have to just match the
colors.
This is good training, by the way. I'm
glad I got a pro Japanese player.
Okay, I almost Oh
he's uh he's on attacking.
Then I'm going to attack him. Knee.
I need one more. Come on. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Yes.
Yes. No. No. I was so close.
Back to lobby.
H.
Thank you for Oh, he left.
I got cooked. How did I Wait, this guy
is still here.
Everyone margin
rate three.
Will he play with me?
Hi.
This ranked in this game.
You can compete in the leaderboards. Oh,
it's Sonic.
Oh I didn't mean to do that. Okay.
Taa.
Ah, that was so dumb.
>> Oh, it has begun. It has begun. It has
begun.
>> It has begun. Oh god.
>> Don't worry.
I'm going to get you, bro.
Uh, he's he's going to go on attackive.
Oh I still have a chance. I still
have a chance.
Still have a chance.
I still have a chance.
>> Give me right. Give me right. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
>> Yes.
I've improved, brother. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
I did it. I didn't let him combo
mass combo me.
I did not let a mouse combo me.
Oh that was that was dumb. That
was dumb. Okay, jump.
Good.
It's
itsy
I'm defeating him.
>> Yes. Oh my god.
Um
Oh my god, guys. Are you seeing this?
Yay. Yay. Yay. Yay. Yaba yaba. I'm
getting better.
Are you witnessing
Mina?
Uh,
it's it's
I think this was a mistake.
>> I shouldn't have cleaned it out. I
shouldn't have cleaned it out. Gosh,
that was a mistake. He He got He got
this round.
He got this run.
>> Oh, he got this run. I was early. I was
early.
Oh
Nice job, bro.
Uh
yeah. Hey
Bro, what am I doing?
Don't let him combo. Don't let him
combo. Do not let him combo.
Do not let him combo.
>> If you let him combo, you're dead.
>> Ah.
Shinda shinda.
>> I let him combo.
H. Oh god. Oh god. I
The way looks like I think I'm going to
die.
Yeah,
black.
It's
>> Don't overshoot it.
You can now.
I will shoot him. Yeah,
it's fine. Do it.
Do it.
No. Oh, wait. I think I got it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No.
This guy is so strong.
Seven chains.
He left.
Am I the only one here?
Hello, welcome
worldwide.
Just dropping by here
by all.
What are you uh what is this game about?
It's It's like Tetris but with a with
like some cute characters.
Yeah, it's literally Tetris and Candy
Crush. Similar to that you
um
match color match actually stuff and do
it.
So there is a tournament hosted by Vak
India on 18th of October on a Sunday at
7:30 p.m. ISG. So I'm participating in
that tournament. So I'm like um
practicing
for this.
Yeah.
I know it is here.
We put broadcast to
Can we watch other people?
Let's watch this guy.
Is it recording though?
Look at these guys. The way they are
playing though.
pop to make a fortune.
>> Look at him play.
How do you know where to target
the prediction though?
Is it?
Oh my
good lord.
guy's a pro.
There's a prediction thingy on
there. That's a prediction thingy on.
That's why I think
I kind of old time, huh?
I kind of understood.
I'll explain the CP version.
Um,
is there anyone here? Wait,
someone is here in the room.
Oh,
someone from Ku
Japan.
Holy lord. That's a
I've been krah.
He kicked me. What the hell,
bro? He kicked me.
What the hell?
He That guy kicked me. The hell did I do
to him?
I going to
uh And
there are no people in the fever.
Oh.
Oh
Tik Tok. Someone from Tik Tok.
Yuru. It's a Japanese brother.
It's
quick.
Or should I die?
It's it's
it's
Itsy
itsy.
>> Oh no.
It's
>> Oh
>> Oh, no.
It's It's
>> It's
no
He got free points. Rang up.
Oh, my rating went down.
Fore!
Foreign! Foreign!
Yahoo!
IT'S
NOT
BRO, WHAT THE HELL?
Oh my lord,
I died.
I have to defeat him. How
Uh
it's
Itsyhe
It's
>> It's It'sy.
No. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
>> I just need a It's one v one. No. One
one.
Oh god. He's He's speeding up. He's
speeding up. Yono
quiet.
>> Oh god,
>> he's sending threats at me. Oh lord.
It's
>> a bro.
Brother in Christ.
He
my rating is lowered.
I don't want to play with him.
The hell
filters.
Oh my god.
Oh my, I just played with the top top
number four player in the world.
A grandmaster
who just No, no. Earlier the Gohan guy
was the grandmaster. Oh my god.
How do you say it?
Okay,
replay is the best.
Yeah,
it's secret.
It's
>> Oh
I didn't even
It's great.
Itsy
item.
Oh no.
Ah,
>> he won.
One more.
Oh no. What?
Oh
Broch.
These players are crazy
and I'm having a really bad cold.
It's weather. The weather is so cold,
too.
Stop sending threats,
>> bro.
No.
>> Hello, Vic. Oh my god, it's Dick. Hello.
How are you doing?
It's been a while.
How you doing, Rick?
I couldn't do that. Okay.
Uh
oh, he's sending attacks at me. Oh.
Oh my god. Wait. I don't know.
Uh,
please, please, please, please.
No.
Um
what idle stuff and then I'm fine. This
is okay.
We also doing well. It's uh cold over
here.
What's the weather in Japan right now?
20°.
Cold.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
>> He dropped me.
Ah, he dropped it.
Connection. I think he all that Ford.
What the hell? He's like, I don't want
to play with the newbie.
I need to learn how the game and play
the game.
Let's watch this
tutorial.
Hi
Ready?
Special controls.
Even faster way to drop your sensor is
basically
they call this quick drop.
Jesus.
This is the chain and they send me the
keys to mushroom field.
I just score a chain score more points.
I found the jeans also some go
up to disappear James
T.
Oh,
simultaneous clear. Oh,
neutralizing.
We call this new choice.
What do you do?
I put that. Oh, okay.
You can neutralize them before.
Oh.
Oh,
okay. That is neutralizing.
Quick one
wrong. If you quickly press the right
person ZX control key twice can rotate
the P.
Oh,
interesting.
It is false.
You can score bonus points. Oh,
saving up chains.
couple of few pure drops ending up here
for easy chains. Okay.
Okay.
Huh.
That's the end of the intermediate.
Creating multiple chains is the key,
too.
Oh, bro. This is so hard.
Okay,
come on this side.
Wait,
is there no one else playing this game
today?
If there people playing, I would want to
play and battle them.
I have to learn how to do this. Bro, at
this point, I don't think I can
win the tournament or the team. I will
be a disappointment for my team. I mean,
and this is day one though. But I think
I just have to keep on playing and
playing and um understand
the game.
We'll eventually get it.
Um,
one second. Let me check. Uh,
if anyone from
is anyone I know streaming
dish
like
Oh, wait. As first room filming.
Oh, wait. What time is it for people?
Ah, it's 8:00 p.m. for them. Um, it's 12
for me. I forgot Japan time and Indian
time is
uh different
times on
most people get uh start their stream at
10 or 9.
Little battle.
Learn to make chains. That's the
victory. That's the goal to victory.
Learn to make chains. Talk next.
Got to make them chains.
Uh,
Oh
>> Oh, no. No, no, no. I I was trying to
combo. Come on. I was trying to
I was trying to combo.
chat.
See if you
Interesting.
Itsy
didn't do it.
Uh
something like uh
I'm not trying I I'm not supposed to try
to clear it. I'm supposed to build up
chains. Don't forget
build up chains. Dark legs.
Yes. Keep going.
>> Keep going. Learn how to build up
chains. That's how you'll
understand.
Uh
uh. What the
I need space.
>> I can defeat him. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's how you do legs. Yeah.
Good, good, good, good, good. Yeah.
Yeah. Slow and steady wins the race
slowly.
Surely
I'll try to play this game tomorrow. No,
not tomorrow. I want to play some FPS
tomorrow. Yeah, I'll try to play this
game on weekends.
Uh, no, on weekdays.
Oh, yeah. Monday I don't have class.
Yeah. Uh, so I can find some time. I
need to find some time to tournament.
Oh no. Oh, he's attacking. He's
attacking.
Let me just kill him fully.
>> I'll just kill him.
>> Okay, good. Oh my god. I And I I learned
the game. No, wait. No, no.
Don't be cocky.
Take it slow.
Oh
Could have
it.
I can actually do it.
It's about doing, you know, I'm not
supposed to do it early.
Feel like I'm doing the early combos,
which is bad. I have to wait for my
opponent.
>> Yeah, I'm trying to do a early
stuff that is wrong.
>> Oh my god, my
uh
Oh god, he got in.
Okay.
It's
slow and steady.
Itsy.
>> Oh
>> No.
Oh, I might have messed up.
I made a mess up.
Okay, I think we can do one last game
and I can wrap up. It's It's going to be
It's It's 1 It's going to be 12:30.
Yeah, I
I know I could keep on playing, but um
yeah,
sure. I know tomorrow is a Sunday.
And yeah, for those who don't know, I
Well, I think I didn't tweet. Oh, I
forgot. So, um, for those who didn't
know, my cycle got stolen recently.
So, I'm buying a new cycle bicycle
tomorrow
at 10 in the morning. Um, so after I get
my cycle and stuff, I think I'll start
streaming.
Um, I'm thinking of streaming. Um
um
the thing is when during weekends,
right, I won like some have like a
shooter game. I need my FPS pew pew.
But lately I've been pew pewing so much,
right?
So, I was thinking
um I was thinking I could uh go with
either this game for like 6 hours, six
or eight hours.
Not that long, but it's a Sunday, so
might have to go out to buy stuff
uh and stuff. I I don't I do not know my
schedule for tomorrow. I don't even
think I can do like more than 4 hour
shrimp, but
even at nights I my roommate
uh and I we um he will help prepare the
dinner and
uh by 9 or 10 I I'll get free if he is
going to
uh go sleep early.
So,
um
I could stream from 10 like today's
stream from 10 to 12,
but
yeah, short streams are pain.
Also, I just noticed
I noticed something.
The game goes quiet when you are all
tabbing.
Why is it that?
Why is it like that?
It was windowed.
Does it act the same? Ah, it does.
Uh,
wait. Why is it like that? Oh,
wait. Why is it like that?
Why is it like that?
Okay. Is there a way I could
Let me check. uh for you for your
champions
game.
Is there a way to
uh
when I'm not
focused?
Uh mute window lo
and focus loss is actually for the game.
Uh,
is there a way I could
do something?
Um,
virtual desktop.
No, it
it's doesn't
have audio on
wireless.
Wait
full screen windowed to how do I make it
like have audio
has a hardcoded for mute build directly
in the game engine. Oh.
Uh
uh
audio routing cable. No,
I mean it's fine I guess if it's silent,
right?
Uh
there is a auto hotkey
uh script for this.
I can make it think I am focused on it.
that way. There is still audio,
but I'm worried if I get cuz this is a
this game has esports and stuff
apparently,
competitions and stuff. So, I'm like
thinking like
is it safe for me to do that?
I know.
Um
we p
How about that?
Let me do something. One second.
Okay. Wait.
Uh,
how do I
Oh Wait, how do I run this?
Uh,
loading. Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. I fixed it. Oh my
god. Okay. Auto hotkey. Thank you. So,
I'm I'm literally not focused on the
game, but
uh the game thinks I'm focused on it,
but I'm not. That way you can you guys
on stream can hear the audio. It
wouldn't sound like I'm all tabbing.
That is nice.
That is actually nice.
We figured out something. He
get qui.
Uh, no.
Uh. Oh, full screen doesn't work. Oh,
isn't this like a old game?
So for screen optimization when Oh yeah,
that will
is it me or when I put it on 1080p
the stuff looks blurry.
Or is it just me? Why does the text and
everything looks blurry?
Hey,
Wait, am I?
Yeah, this is clear. This is clear.
Clear. Clear. Okay,
watch this.
Hey, switch to this. It's start going to
start becoming blurry. Okay.
See, it's blurry.
It wor.
And why?
Why though?
Hey, why does it do that?
Hey,
wait. Alt enter. No, no, wait.
Wait, wait, wait. What was the command?
Control enter. No, hold
alt enter.
Ah, it forces forced.
Hey, why is it blurry though?
Why is it blurry though?
Oh, that is so weird.
If it's blurry like this, can't I like
go to in game files and like
uh is it not something like that? No,
nothing
like config something. Uh no. Okay, it
doesn't have it.
Yeah.
Yep. They do not have it, it seems.
Why was same games?
Oh,
usually it's supposed to be there in the
save folder or something.
Uh,
I can't find it.
Wait, Sega, right? So, let's see.
Oh, it's over here. Wow.
What the
local?
Oh, it's Sega S
or P Pew Pew.
Oh, yes.
Config
file. Okay.
With the game just Okay.
Okay. Graphics config. Oh,
okay. Okay. So, what it'll do is 1920 by
full screen one go one full screen width
of V6 one and uh
save this and
save this and right click and
mark as read Finally apply
quit to desktop
and I'll launch the game again.
And it should now give me uh 1080p
quality on a window at full screen
if I'm correct.
Yes.
Oh my god, I'm a genius.
No, it's not nothing about genius or
anything. It's just what it is there out
there for other games.
See, it's not blurry anymore. The boxes.
All right, there is a little bit of
blurriness. You see the ones over here?
One, one X.
Oh no. Is it that blurry?
It's not that blurry.
It's not that blurry, so it's fine.
Anyone know?
Uh let's uh
let us
wrap up. I guess
I can't
for tonight.
It is late.
Titan.
Uh I
will continue in the next PP stream.
Okay.
Uh let me switch to the game scene. I
know talking scene.
My nose is blocked. Oh god, I've been
sneezing.
on stream and off stream. We have about
while muted the I muted the mic and was
sneezing so much.
It is
but yeah. Um
I I just want to say that like I
I'll be streaming more of this game. I
need to get used to
um used to the game and learn how to do
the uh chains and everything.
Uh, that would mean I have to use my
brain a lot,
but it's a fun game. It gives you like a
uh
it may it trains your brain to think
which colors can which pattern can go
well with this. Why? How should you
place the placement of the block? Uh the
pu or blocks. It's literally Tetris you
can say. Yeah. The more I play this
game, I feel like I should
try to play by one day play sandress
or something. There's a sand tress
thingy that's also similar like this.
It's fun.
You can
uh you know match the colors and
make them
chain attack all those stuff.
Same stuff like neutralization and quick
quick move quick
stuff like that. I just really
interesting.
Um,
forgot my phone notifications.
Yeah,
a second.
Uh,
but yeah, today was fun. And I
got to
try out this game finally. Apparently
now uh everyone who are participating in
the tournament from India uh most of
them it's the game is like 250
rupees or something because of the 50%
off going on for this game on Steam for
the autumn sale.
So, since I'm in Japan, due to a
regional difference, uh the tournament
organizers organizers, they uh tried to
send me the free game copy cuz I'm a
participant, but they couldn't gift me.
I couldn't accept the gift because of
the regional thingy.
Apparently, if you didn't know, like on
Steam, they do allow cross region
gifting, but the issue is more like
if a game has regional restrictions.
For example, this game is from Sega,
right? Yeah. So, Sega had regional
restrictions for this game. That's why
um
it it defaulted uh the Steam uh yeah if
a game publisher has regional uh
limitations
uh restrictions like that it will
default
back to the old thingy. Uh so you cannot
do cross gifting
or something. That's what let me when I
asked like
to in Google search it just said me that
apparently someone talked about this in
like for other games and also some
somewhere in Reddit I guess. I'm not
sure but yeah that happened. So, I was
given like a gift card,
the 640 yen gift card since in uh this
game in Japan is like 720
yen.
That's like in Indian rupees that's like
around
500 600 rupees
double the amount of what you are able
to buy from India for like 250 rupees.
Why is Japanese yen so like expensive
and like I don't get it too much though.
Too much. Did you know today
um my my room couldn't cycles
um tire the back tire was not um like I
think uh it's a punch or something
apparently just to change your tires
tube
here in Japan they took 6,000 yen
like back in India and stuff right like
If you need to change your tire or the
tube and stuff, it's going to be under
2,000 or 1,000. Under,000.
It won't go above that.
6,000 yen is literally
3,7
rounding up to say 3,700
rupees.
Crazy, man. No, it it it costed around
7,000 service charge. Oh yeah.
Stupid service charge. Yeah, 4,000
rupees. Crazy, man. Crazy.
I don't know what to say. Everything is
expensive here though.
God, my boys too.
Come up.
I have I have to be more quieter.
My roommates are sleeping cuz I have to
be more quieter.
Yeah.
So that
Uh but yeah, I'll
let you guys know what I'll stream
tomorrow. Okay,
till then.
Thank you for today. I mean, uh
Oh, my my nose is stuffed. Stuffy. What
the hell?
Yeah, but
my also stuffed up. Oh god. You can you
can hear it from my voice. Oh lord.
Yeah, but
Oh god, my nose is stuffed up. Oh god.
Oh god.
I can't breathe. Yeah.
Hey, my internet is dying.
internet.
Oh god, my internet again.
Am I live?
Yeah, you guys are delayed by two
minutes.
Okay, I think I'm going to wrap it up
here. Sorry, I'm sneezing a lot.
Yeah, I'm going to wrap it up over here.
I'm sneezing a lot.
Wait.
Yeah, this is getting worse. I'm
sneezing so much. So, yeah.
Please allow me to speak of my God.
Okay. Uh God, I can't even speak. Every
second he speak, open my mouth, I'm
sneezing.
Okay. Uh thank you again to those who
came by today. Let me read your names.
Thank you, Victor.
Thank you, Alasa. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, Maya, for coming by.
Then, um, Alisan, thank you for coming
by. Roan, thank you for coming by. Thank
you for coming by.
And old
All the lurkers
who were lurking on YouTube and Twitter
and Rumble. Thank you so much for
watching the stream. It really really
means a lot.
Yeah. Bye.
My throat is dying.
So yeah, once again, thank you for
coming. I'll stream again in the next
time. I'll notify you guys on Discord,
Twitter, or in Instagram stories and
stuff. So yeah.
Hi.
Um I think I'm sick. I have to take some
medicine. Uh this is bad. The weather is
getting more colder and colder. Um,
yeah, I hate the winter, but it's good.
But yeah, I hate when I have cold.
I got to drink some hot water and stuff.
Yeah, this is this is so bad. Yeah, but
yeah, thank you again. Have a good one,
everyone. Have a good night ahead.
Bye-bye.
Boy, my boy